<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="146044" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Hover Colors" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
    <ShortDescription Value="Change blue outlines to any color or opacity. Surface layers on/off, District colors."/>
    <!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
<LongDescription>
    ## Mochi's Hover Colors

    **Major additions in 0.9.0 update**: please check new city Hover Color panel
    - added color swatches + tooltips and more choices in the mod's Options menu!

    - Change the blue outline color that has haunted every part of your city.
    - If you can hover over it then you can probably change it: buildings, cars, trees, cims, etc.!
    - Guidelines: change opacity so you can see items being placed and not just a thick white line!
    - Surfaces: turn off preview layers while using the Surface tool so you can see the real ground colors without a cloudy layer on top.
    - District tool: change the color + opacity of district borders and overlays, or turn them off completely.

    ## Important
    - Check the Options menu for bulldozer and road-tool color behavior.
    - To turn off panel tooltips, click the Info button in the top-left of the in-city panel.
    - **Darker panel** option. Recommended for LegacyUI or players who prefer darker high contrast. Try both panels and see what you like!
    - Alpha is transparency; it's the last bar on the color picker.
    - Tap preset 1 or 2 to switch your saved colors.
    - Change presets: select a color from the main color picker, then hold preset 1 or 2 until the fill bar completes.
    - Hotkeys are in the Options menu. Read the tooltips or Options Menu 3rd panel if you get lost.
    - Save-game safe and safe to remove any time.
    - No known compatibility issues. No Harmony patches.
    - Performance Optimized: when the panel is closed, it is not doing active layout work;
    the C# systems mostly sit idle unless a relevant state changes, example, you change a color, mod takes action, then goes back idle.


    ### Feedback

    - Please send suggestions, bug reports, or just say hi!
    - This mod took many months to overcome many obstacles in game code.
    - This is a passion project and I want to make it the best it can be,
    so please share your thoughts and suggestions! -- River Mochi


    ## ❤️ Special Thanks
    * Huge shout out to everyone who tested or supported the mod on its long journey to release*
    - Flashbond - collab, tech feedback, testing
    - yenyang - collab, tech feedback, testing
    - StarQ - tech feedback, testing
    - gagaxm - feature idea, testing
    - Dx, Necko1996, BugsyG, ElGendo87 - testing
    - =Noel= Thumbnail, testing

    ### 15+ Languages
    - English, Français, Deutsch, Español, Italiano, Polski, 简体中文 , 한국어
    - Português Brasil, 繁體中文 , 日本語
    WIP: Thai ภาษาไทย, Vietnamese Tiếng Việt, Turkish Türkçe, EU Portuguese Português

    tags: Mochi's blue scrubber, Highlight, border color, remove blue, guidelines, district colors, surface tool, custom colors, transparency.

</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail-building_cyan.jpg" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/12-image-before-after.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/15-image-Options.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/20-image-ColorPicker.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/30-image-Guidelines.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/40-image-DistrictColorPicker.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/50-image-Districts.jpg" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/mochis-hover-colors.1925898/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="0.9.0" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.5.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Required DLC, can be set multiple times. Supported values are "Landmark Buildings", "San Fransisco Set", "Beach Properties", "Urban Promenades", "Modern Architecture"-->
	<RequiredDLC Value="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
<ChangeLog>
- UI/UX improvements
- added 3 Guide line color preset swatches to customize the new road tool (for circles with spacing lines and road overlay color).
- clicking on Guideline icon button resets to vanilla colors all guidelines and road overlays (usually cyan).
- updated translations.
- District tool: added reset to vanilla.
- main keybind changed to "J". Now have "J", ""K", and "L" hotkeys - change or remove these in HC Options menu.
</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link, can be set multiple times. supported types are "discord", "github", "youtube", "twitch", "x", "paypal", "patreon", "buymeacoffee", "kofi", "crowdin", "gitlab", "gofundme"-->
	<ExternalLink Type="" Url="" />
    <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/River-Mochi/HoverColors" />
    <ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />

	<!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
	<AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
